Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
[Episode 8]
[الحلقة 8]
This affair ends now
هذه القضية تنتهي الآن
in your own room!
في غرفتك الخاصة!
I think
أظن
you know
أنت تعرف
why Wang Wan'er invited you.
لماذا دعتك وانغ وان إير.
You don't wanna marry her, right?
أنت لا تريد الزواج منها، أليس كذلك؟
You're looking for Qingmao, right?
أنت تبحث عن تشينغماو، أليس كذلك؟
Listen.
يستمع.
Work with me.
اعمل معي.
I'll tell you
سأخبرك
how the Wangs killed her.
كيف قتلها الوانج.
Do as you please.
افعل ما يحلو لك.
You wretch!
أيها الوغد!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Anger doesn't suit your beauty.
الغضب لا يناسب جمالك .
Liu Rumeng!
ليو رومينج!
How dare you seduce Wenbin?
كيف تجرؤ على إغواء وينبين؟
At the Paramount,
في باراماونت،
all guests are welcome.
جميع الضيوف مرحب بهم.
Wenbin
وينبين
is no exception.
ليس استثناء.
You've been playing me all along?
هل كنت تلعب معي طوال الوقت؟
Unlike you, Miss Wang,
على عكسك، يا آنسة وانغ،
you annoyed him with all your schemes.
لقد أزعجته بكل مخططاتك.
It's a bother for me
إنه أمر مزعج بالنسبة لي
that I did nothing
أنني لم أفعل شيئا
yet Wenbin keeps pursuing me.
ومع ذلك، يستمر وينبين في مطاردتي.
The Blycher Hotel.
فندق بليشر.
The Paramount.
الباراماونت.
Even in your room.
حتى في غرفتك.
He's so bold.
إنه جريء جدًا.
Every time,
في كل مرة،
right under your nose.
تحت أنفك مباشرة.
It's thrilling,
إنه أمر مثير
really.
حقًا.
You're such a good friend to me.
أنت صديق جيد جدًا بالنسبة لي.
You always do what I say,
أنت تفعل دائمًا ما أقوله،
in business and life.
في العمل والحياة.
The lost shipment,
الشحنة المفقودة
today's party disaster, all of it.
كارثة الحفلة اليوم، كلها.
I'm so worried about you.
أنا قلقة عليك جدًا.
You did this
لقد فعلت هذا
on purpose, right?
عن قصد، أليس كذلك؟
Liu Rumeng,
ليو رومينج,
our opium
أفيوننا
is in your hands, right?
هو في يديك، أليس كذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
The Wangs were secretly
كان آل وانغ سراً
transporting opium?
نقل الأفيون؟
Scared?
مقدس؟
Without you,
بدونك،
we wouldn't need
لن نحتاج
investment from the Chamber
استثمار من الغرفة
to cover the opium loss.
لتغطية خسائر الأفيون.
Hand over
تسليم
the opium now.
الأفيون الآن.
Or I'll
أو سأفعل
burn the Paramount down.
أحرقوا الباراماونت.
Don't cross the Wang family.
لا تتعدى على عائلة وانغ.
I never thought
لم افكر ابدا
you could be so vile!
يمكنك أن تكون شريرًا جدًا!
Aren't you afraid of karma?
ألا تخاف من الكارما؟
Karma?
كارما؟
Where is it?
أين هي؟
I don't see it!
انا لا ارى ذلك!
You're not the first ghost
أنت لست الشبح الأول
our Wangs have made!
لقد صنعنا وانج!
Miss Wang is a murderer!
السيدة وانغ قاتلة!
Stop filming!
اوقف التصوير!
Stop!
قف!
I'll kill you all!
سأقتلكم جميعا!
Enough!
كافٍ!
Dad.
أب.
I can let her go.
أستطيع أن أتركها تذهب.
But you cover the debt.
ولكنك تغطي الدين.
Yes, yes!
نعم نعم!
I have one last opium batch.
لدي دفعة أخيرة من الأفيون.
Just grant me dock access,
فقط امنحني حق الوصول إلى الرصيف،
and I'll repay you, I swear!
وسأكافئك، أقسم بذلك!
Be smart. No next time.
كن ذكيا. لا مرة أخرى.
Dad!
أب!
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Speak! What happened?
تكلم! ماذا حدث؟
We...
نحن...
We're expelled from the Chamber.
لقد تم طردنا من الغرفة.
And...
و...
No dock will take our goods.
لن يقبل أي رصيف بضائعنا.
You dare face me?
هل تجرؤ على مواجهتي؟
Don't you know
ألا تعلم؟
why we're in this mess?
لماذا نحن في هذه الفوضى؟
I told you explicitly
لقد قلت لك صراحة
to keep our business secret!
للحفاظ على سرية أعمالنا!
But you just wouldn't listen!
ولكنك لم تستمع!
You ignored my words!
لقد تجاهلت كلامي!
If I hadn't stopped you,
لو لم أوقفك،
would you have
هل سيكون لديك
blabbed about my past, too?
هل تحدثت عن ماضي أيضًا؟
You'll be the death of me!
سوف تكون سبب موتي!
No!
لا!
It wasn't me, Dad!
لم أكن أنا يا أبي!
It's Liu Rumeng! All her doing!
إنها ليو رومينغ! كل هذا بفضلها!
Liu Rumeng! Liu Rumeng!
ليو رومينج! ليو رومينج!
She played you for a fool!
لقد لعبت بك كأحمق!
If you had half her wits,
لو كان لديك نصف ذكائها،
you wouldn't be...
لن تكون...
Get out!
اخرج!
Liu Rumeng.
ليو رومينج.
You came alone.
لقد أتيت وحدك.
Aren't you afraid?
ألا تخافين؟
I've done nothing wrong.
لم أفعل شيئا خاطئا.
Why should I be afraid?
لماذا يجب أن أكون خائفا؟
Good.
جيد.
You have some nerve.
لديك بعض الشجاعة.
Now give me one reason
الآن أعطني سبب واحد
not to kill you.
لا لقتلك.
There's a misunderstanding between us.
هناك سوء تفاهم بيننا.
What misunderstanding?
ما هذا سوء الفهم؟
Miss Wang's effort to fix business flaws
جهود السيدة وانغ لإصلاح عيوب الأعمال
were found by the Marshal.
تم العثور عليها من قبل المارشال.
I tried to help fix it,
لقد حاولت المساعدة في إصلاحه،
which made her jealous.
مما جعلها تشعر بالغيرة.
That caused all this.
وهذا ما تسبب في كل هذا.
I overstepped.
لقد تجاوزت.
So I came here
لذلك جئت إلى هنا
to apologize.
للاعتذار.
Apologize?
يعتذر؟
Besides the Paramount,
بالإضافة إلى باراماونت،
I own a dock in Song City.
أملك رصيفًا في مدينة سونغ.
How did you know
كيف عرفت
I need a dock right now?
أحتاج إلى رصيف الآن؟
This is all I own.
هذا كل ما أملكه.
I'll pay any price
سأدفع أي ثمن
for a chance to live.
للحصول على فرصة للعيش.
I have a shipment.
لدي شحنة.
I'll use your dock.
سأستخدم قفص الاتهام الخاص بك.
And you'll oversee it personally,
وسوف تشرف عليه شخصيا،
and bring it back intact.
وإعادته سليما.
That is your final chance.
هذه فرصتك الاخيرة
Deal.
اتفاق.
Liu Rumeng, I will make you pay.
ليو رومينج، سأجعلك تدفع الثمن.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪